http://www.mater.org.au/group/terms

Search for:
Mater
AboutMater Hill Master PlanOur brandOur governanceOur heritageOur strategyOur sustainabilityMater Early LearningMissionValuesVisionNewsMater newsPublicationsSocial mediaCareersRegistered Nurse and Midwifery Graduate ProgramMedical Officer recruitmentTraining and educationVolunteeringWorking with MaterCurrent VacanciesOur communitySupport
Health
AboutCareersCredentialingSafety and performanceHospitalsServicesAll ServicesCancer ServicesGynaecological oncologyMater at HomeMater Intellectual Disability and Autism ServiceMater Kidney Health ServiceMater PathologyMater PharmacyMater Young Adult Health CentreMater/UQ Centre for Integrated Care and InnovationMaternityNeurosciencesFor patientsSupport
Education
CoursesClinical supervision & communicationClinical trainingGP educationMaternity & infant careQualificationsResus & life supportSimulation faculty developmentSimulationExperiential orientationFacilities testingProcedure rehearsalPrototype consultationSystems testingSimulation servicesStay up to date
Research
ResearchBiobanksClinical trialsClinical trials for industry sponsorsParticipate in research at MaterResearch programsResearch projectsResearchersOur researchersFor researchersAboutOur governanceGender equity initiativeSupport usSupport
Foundation
About
In an emergency
Contact
We are an iconic provider of hospital-based healthcare, striving to deliver an exceptional standard of care
We comprise several hospitals, health centres, a nationally accredited education provider and a world-class research institute
We are a nationally accredited, hospital-based Registered Training Organisation - the only one of its kind in Queensland
We are part of a collaborative research institute with The University of Queensland and founding partner of the Translational Research Institute
About
Mater Hill Master Plan
About the Master Plan
Community engagement
Frequently Asked Questions (FAQs)
Planning beyond 2030
Proposed initiatives
Our brand
History of the Mater Cross
Our governance
Mercy Partners
Our heritage
Archives and Heritage Centre
Acceptance of Website Terms and Conditions of Use
By using this site you agree to abide by these Website Terms & Conditions.  Mater  may, without notice, amend or modify its Website Terms & Conditions by posting the amended Terms & Conditions to this website.
If any of these Website Terms & Conditions is found to be invalid or unenforceable, that invalidity or unenforceability will not affect the remainder of the Terms & Conditions, which will continue in full force and effect.
Ownership
This website is owned and operated by Mater as trustee for Mater Misericordiae Limited (ACN 096 708 922) (hereinafter referred to as "Mater", "we", "us" and “our”).
Intended audience
All information provided on this website has been prepared in accordance with Australian law, and is intended for use by residents of Australia.  Persons residing outside of Australia use this website at their own risk, and should take into consideration the legislative requirements of their country of residence when accessing this website.  Should you choose to purchase products from Mater Foundation, or make a donation to us, you should confirm that doing so will not constitute a contravention of the laws of your country of residence.
Restrictions on Use
All information provided on this website has been provided for personal and non-commercial use.  It is general information only, and should not be relied upon in lieu of professional and/or medical advice.
Please consult your healthcare provider if you have, or suspect you have, a health problem.
The information on this website is obtained and developed from a variety of sources including but not limited to collaborations with third parties and information provided by third parties under licence. Where the health information provided has been developed by Mater Research, whether in its own right or in conjunction with any third party, that information is based on independent research and the available scientific evidence at the time of writing. Inclusion of information on this website or links to third party sites is not an endorsement of any organisation, product or service.
Whilst care has been taken in preparing the content of the material and any other information provided on this website, Mater and its employees, related parties, directors, officers, committee members, servants, agents, volunteers, contractors, subcontractors and collaborators cannot accept any liability, including for any loss or damage, resulting from the reliance on the content, or for its accuracy, currency and completeness.
Any use of Mater materials or information by another person or organisation is at the user's own risk.
Copyright and Trademarking
Mater supports and encourages the dissemination and exchange of information. However, copyright protects material on this website. Mater asserts the right to be recognised as the author of this material and the right to have its material remain unaltered.
Except for purposes permitted by the Copyright Act 1968, or in accordance with the copyright statements appearing on the individual web pages, reproduction by whatever means is prohibited without the prior written permission of Mater.
Mater Little Miracles® is registered to with iPAustralia and owned by Mater Misericordiae Limited.
International Women’s Day Fun Run is pending registration approval with iPAustralia and owned by Mater Hospitals’ Appeal Ltd.
Indemnity, Disclaimer and Limitation of Liability
Whilst due care has been taken in the preparation of the content of this website we make no representations regarding the accuracy, currency or reliability of the information provided unless otherwise indicated, and note there may be errors, omissions and typographical errors contained in the material provided.
This website and the material it contains are provided on an as-is basis, and to the fullest extent permitted by law we disclaim all warranties. In addition we do not warrant that this website is error free or that the website and/or the servers it is hosted on are free of viruses, Trojans or other malicious software.
Mater and its employees, directors, officers, committee members, servants, agents, volunteers, contractors, subcontractors and collaborators will not be liable for any loss or damage other than that which cannot be excluded by law arising as a result of use of this website or reliance on any information provided on this website.
You agree to indemnify Mater including its employees, directors, officers, committee members, servants, agents, volunteers, contractors, subcontractors and collaborators from any loss or damage which it may suffer as a result of your use of this website.
Hyperlinks, Advertising, Sponsors and Third Party Content
This website may contain the content of third parties (Third Party Content).  This content may include, but is not limited to hyperlinks to external (third party) websites, or program sponsors.  None of these things is to be taken as an endorsement, recommendation or approval of the third party, or sponsor or their products or services.  Mater accepts no responsibility for the accuracy, currency or suitability or otherwise regarding Third Party Content.  Any use or reliance on such content is at your own risk and Mater does not accept liability for any loss, damage, costs or expenses arising as a result of the use or reliance.
Where hyperlinks to third party websites are provided, Mater makes no claims regarding the suitability or otherwise of the third party’s products or services to your needs, nor does it warrant the third party website is free of viruses, Trojans or other malicious software.
Should you have any queries, concerns or complaints regarding a third party’s website please refer your query, concern or complaint to the third party.
Mater’s logo must not be reproduced or used in any way unless Mater provides its prior approval in writing.
Should you wish to provide a link to this website from another site you may do so provided you adhere to the following terms and conditions:
Terms and Conditions for providing a link to this website from another site
Permission is granted to link to this website subject to the following terms and conditions:
No responsibility or liability lies with Mater (or any employee, agent or servant) for any errors or omissions resulting from use of this website.
Under no circumstances should your site use the link to Mater website to provide specific product or service endorsement or promotion. Nor should the link be placed to imply product or service endorsement or be associated with commercial interests.
When applicable, the following wording is to be used to describe the website:
Mater's Vision is to be a leading health-based organisation, trusted by community and renowned for investing in a future of exceptional healthcare, education and medical research.
Donations to Mater Foundation help improve patient care, purchase life-saving medical equipment, and ensure our research teams continue to find better ways to diagnose, treat and ultimately cure life-threatening diseases.
Mater Foundation reserves the right to withdraw permission to link to this website at any time and the above named organisation agrees to remove any link to this website on receiving such notice from Mater Foundation.
No information, in whole or in part, is to be copied from the website without Mater Foundation’s prior consent in writing.
Jurisdiction
These terms and conditions are governed by and to be interpreted in accordance with the laws in force in the State of Queensland, Australia and in the event of any dispute arising in relation to these terms and conditions or any dispute arising in relation to the Internet Site whether in contract or tort or otherwise the Courts of Queensland and any Courts competent to hear appeals therefrom will have non-exclusive jurisdiction over such dispute.
Cookies
We use "cookies" as a fundamental part of our interaction with your Internet browser. The purpose is to provide you with better and more customised service and with a more effective Mater website.
A "cookie" is a small text file placed on your computer by our web page server. A cookie can later be retrieved by our webpage servers. Cookies are frequently used on web sites and you can choose if and how a cookie will be accepted by configuring your preferences and options in your browser.
We allocate a cookie to each Internet browser that visits Mater’s website. This cookie does not allow us to collect personally identifiable information about you.
We use this cookie:
To determine if you have previously visited the Mater site;
To identify pages you have accessed and Third Party Sites you have accessed;
For marketing purpose; and
For administrative and security purposes.
Privacy Policy and Notification Statement
Mater (ACN 096 708 922) is committed to protecting your privacy.
Our Privacy Policy is aligned with the Australian Privacy Principles to ensure greater transparency around how we handle your personal information in line with global privacy reforms. Personal information is collected to process donations, issue tax receipts and to send you updates, without this, Mater may be unable to provide you with certain information and offers or meet our legal obligations.
Our Privacy policy and notification statement can be read in full by clicking here.
If you have any questions or concerns, please contact the:
Privacy Coordinator
Privacy Office,
Mater Group
Raymond Terrace, South Brisbane 4101
Tel: 07 3163 2666 Fax: 07 3163 8104
email: privacyoffice@mater.org.au
The Office is located on Level 2 of the Mater Hospital Brisbane
Contact details
Should you have any queries or concerns regarding Mater’s website Terms & Conditions of use please contact Mater Privacy Office, privacyoffice@mater.org.au.
